<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[whyricardoposadasworks]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[whyricardoposadasworks]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/whyricardoposadasworks/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 20:22:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/whyricardoposadasworks/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[My Vision and Personal Mission in Life]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>My Vision and Personal Mission in Life</h1><p>I'm thankful to be a part of all of the lives that have been changed in a positive way over the last few years. Something that started in a moment where change became an absolute necessity has turned into a community that has been a springboard for more people than I can count, and more families than I know. The reason I started is still why I'm here: To win by helping people create what they're here to create --- not just a superficial situational change but a core transformation to walk into their ultimate purpose, whatever that means. At the core of my being I have that written on my heart, and it's why I light up. I'm thankful that the people who I'm connected with are here because they align with that purpose - the purpose of creating real transformation in the lives of real families, real professionals, single Moms and Dads who want a better way. When visions align and connect, they resonate and create a bigger vision like a web of power created from a collective mind. There is power in being there to serve people and walking in your inborn purpose. I could go on and on, and could never thank all of the people who are in this vision with us. You all matter and I appreciate who you are. We are all doing what we do because we love people. And all of you who are in my life now or have been in my life in the past, I am thankful for you. This week I am in a new space because what I had in my heart is coming together. Exactly the way I want. Let's go out into the world and transform families. Let's build a team that dreams together. Let's create products that actually change lives. Let's put our teams first. I used to say: "Let's lock arms, and fight the forces of evil." And something shifted and changed. There's nothing to fight anymore, there's only a vision for the people, to create a team of people winning for the rest of their lives, and growing together through everything. Helping people step into their power. Creating change for their clients first. We will create something different by being something different. We are moving into a new, better, and bigger space --- taking the things we've learned that are powerful and letting go of energy that doesn't serve our vision. Thank you all who are aligned from the heart. You are starting to see it. But something amazing is going to happen to you this week. Watch for it; just continue reading the next two or three posts and maybe once in a while the next 2 or three days until Saturday the 18th of June, 2016.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/4f0b76d4-da0e-416a-8d78-d7849d29378b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/whyricardoposadasworks/my-vision-and-personal-mission-in-life/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1dd65152-27b1-437a-978f-1cb369dfc359</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 20:22:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LaOroyaOldSmelter]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>LaOroyaOldSmelter</h1><p>Uploaded by Ricardo Posadas on 2016-06-16.</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/26f37b5aaa2df98349e12bbefc29c3d2/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=720&cropwidth=961&degrees=0&input=http%3A%2F%2Fimg.youtube.com%2Fvi%2FUNKYkIouvKk%2Fmaxresdefault.jpg&x=160&y=0"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://youtu.be/UNKYkIouvKk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">85466cfb-b2b2-412c-9833-1b4cf86cfa9c</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 05:50:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>